SANDRO DEZERIO

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER



sdezerio@gmail.com

Sandro Dezerio



SandroSD

Dedicated, efficient Developer with 5+ years of professional experience in the build of websites and web applications. Possess excellent knowledge of JavaScript, particularly of React.js and Node.js. Characterized for being result-driven, customer-focused, articulate and analytical developer with solid problem-solving skills. Love performing my job as well as sharing my knowledge with other team workers. Enjoy being part of a group to bring ideas and achieve the best solution.

EXPERIENCE

Distillery (Software Outsourcing)

Jun 2022 - Present

React and Node Developer

Vivo Aquatics. Backend software development for a mobile app, allowing users to manage their bodies of water, equipments and properties depending on their role.

- · Maintain and improve existing software and develop features for the project.
- · Make architectural decisions for the project.
- Write reusable, scalable and easy to follow code with Nest.js (Node.js with Typescript).
- Participate in all meetings helping the team, sharing ideas and points of view.
- Write cloud functions and scheduling triggers in Realm, MongoDB with JavaScript.
- Create CRON functions to manipulate data/information to be executed on its own.
- Write documentation for the project for product owners and stakeholders.
- Create scripts to migrate data from MongoDB from one environment to another.
- Create a module in the API to allow mobile app receiving push notifications with EXPO.
- Perform code review of other members code.

Technologies used. Javascript, Typescript, Node JS, Nest JS, Mongo DB, Mongoose, Realm, Expo (Push Notifications), GraphQL, GraphQL Playground, Jira, GIT.

Edwards Technologies. Backend software development for a mobile app, allowing users to manage content other users of the company can create, update, share or delete, as well as the devices registered in the company. The product is still in development phase.

- Start the backend (built with Amplify framework using AWS) for the mobile app
- Make architectural decisions for the project
- Write reusable and scalable code with Node.js
- Participate in meetings with the team, sharing ideas and points of view
- Maintain (add/update some features) old applications written in Node.js

Technologies used. JavaScript (Node.js), AWS (Amplify, Cognito, DynamoDB, Lambda Functions, S3, API Gateway, Push Notifications)

Fpay (Software Factory)

Oct 2021 - Jun 2022

Fullstack Developer

Creation of a virtual wallet called "Fpay" using different APIs, with an infrastructure based on microservices and AWS.

- Took part in decision-making and meeting schedules
- · Wrote reusable and scalable code with Node.js
- · Wrote unit tests for every developed functionality
- Actively participated in meetings with the team to share ideas
- · Performed reusable and scalable feature design
- · Carried out analysis of documentation for development

Technologies used. Git, Jira, Scrum, JavaScript (Express.js), RabbitMQ, MongoDB, Postman

SoulIT Solutions (IT Services and Consulting)

May 2018 - Oct 2021

Fullstack Developer

Development of management web applications for user and employees to save relevant information and control their jobs, for industries like oil and real estate, providing them with an easy way to save their information and make searches.

- Built Rest API and performed maintenance with Slim (PHP) and Nest.js (Node.js)
- · Attended architectural meetings for the application development
- · Developed web with React.js
- · Maintained applications in C#
- Analyzed and designed documentation for development
- Learned how to use relational database, including MySQL and SQL, connecting it with the backend through technologies previously used to create REST APIs
 to support web applications

Technologies used. Git, Trello, Scrum, PHP (Slim framework), JavaScript (Node.js: Nest.js with TypeScript and Express.js), JavaScript (React, Redux, React Hooks), MySQL, SQL Server, Postman, Material UI

Union Personal (Hospitals and Healthcare)

Jun 2017 - Mar 2018

Web Programmer and Full Stack Developer

Update of the ERP and creation of new functionalities.

- · Used JavaScript and jQuery for the frontend, and employed PHP and MySQL for the backend
- · Created reusable and scalable modules
- · Used Linux Server Administration
- · Created Bash scripts
- All the work was done under Scrum methodology

Technologies used. Git, Trello, PHP, jQuery (JavaScript), SQL (MySQL)

SANDRO DEZERIO FULLSTACK DEVELOPER



Sandro Dezerio



sdezerio@gmail.com



<u>SandroSD</u>

EDUCATION

National Univeristy of La Matanza

2021

Bachelor's Degree in IT Engineering

LANGUAGES

English

B1+ (Intermediate)

SKILLS

HTML 5 | CSS 3 | Javascript | EcmaScript Standarts | React JS | Redux | React Hooks | Typescript | SASS | Bootstrap | Material UI | Tailwind CSS | Node JS | Express JS | Nest JS | API Rest | Graph QL | Microservices | Distributed Systems | Backend | Frontend | FullStack | My SQL | SQL Server | Mongo DB | AWS | Firebase | ORMs | Git | Github | Bitbucket | CI / CD | Pipelines | Unit Testing | Jest